Chuang, Tieh-Hung

ironhead.chuang@gmail.com http://blog.ironhead.ninja/

Summary

Software Developer with 10 years of programming experience. Comfortable in large code bases and multithreading development. Write clear, maintainable code. Excellent debugging skills. Eager to explore new technologies.

Skills

Programming: C/C++, Python, Objective-C, Ruby **Other**: XCode, Visual Studio, Perforce, Git

Work Experience

Freelance, July 2011 - Present.

- Developing assets management software using Django.
- Developed and released P.R.O.B.E., an universal iOS game.
- Developed and released 4x4, an iPhone puzzle game.

Technical Consultant

Next Media Animation, Taipei, Taiwan, July 2012 - Present

- Provided solutions to video playback issues.
- Provided solutions to optimize edge finding and rendering.

R&D Engineer

Next Media Animation, Taipei, Taiwan, August 2009 - June 2011

- Optimized optical flow algorithm using CUDA.
- Developed a DirectShow filter to dump video streams.
- Developed a tool to merge Light Stage scanned faces.
- Presented the CUDA programming guide to the team.
- Presented the HDRI knowledge and algorithm to the team.

Senior Software Engineer

Corel Corporation, Taipei, Taiwan, December 2006 - August 2009

- Developed a TV application for incubation.
- Maintained and extended the in-house D3D skin library.
- Developed a COM component to adjust the brightness of video based on environment lighting.

Software Engineer

InterVideo, Taipei, Taiwan, March 2006 - December 2006

- Maintained a TV and media player application on embedded Windows XP.
- Developed a TV component for application (InterVideo Home Theater).

Software Engineer

DynaColor, Taipei, Taiwan, January 2004 - February 2006

Windows application for Digital Video Recorder

- Developed applications to manage multiple channels and cameras.
- Developed a font editor for OS of digital video recorder.

Education

B.S. in Physics

National Taiwan University, Taipei, Taiwan, June 2001.